[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "... question go ask?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "... it's interesting that you asked that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "POS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 67, "question": "I do find what's happened down there quite fascinating because - with serious question I think should be asked now of the police and their behavior over this shouldn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "IN", ":", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 68, "answer": "Well, you've got a DUI allegation, you're talking about a breath reading that's under the legal limit which is 0.02.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Justin Bieber"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "Is there a serious risk here of Bieber being deported?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, if Justin Bieber is sort of a criminal light right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bieber"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "RB", "WP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 152, "question": "And how did it all go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 153, "answer": "I don't have anything to compare it to but he called 911 and the operator was very helpful just to kind of walk him through how -- I mean that they sure they -- just what exactly to do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "Did you feel like it was unproblematic in the end despite the terrible situation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "It was sheer blessing that everything went well, the girl was healthy and doing great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Atlanta"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Who is ultimately responsible?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, in my case, I mean I don't know Atlanta and the jurisdiction there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "POS", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ":"], "qSentId": 201, "question": "Well, and also I found -- what do I found with gun control?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 202, "answer": "Well, let's see, you have mentioned ...", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "Can he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "No he can't.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [":", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 221, "question": "... do the things he's saying?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 222, "answer": "... half of it will get challenged in the courts, half of it will get all returned as being executive overreach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ronald Reagan", "Bill Clinton"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Can any President in his position right now really achieve a great deal more in the rest of his second term?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RBR", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Ronald Reagan and Bill Clinton did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", ":", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 259, "question": "But what can he do about gun control saying without Congress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 260, "answer": "He can do more -- he can do more enforcement on the justice department.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP$", "NNS", "PRP$", "RB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 273, "question": "Well, it's to do deal, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 274, "answer": "But I have to give away somethings that my constituents my not like.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "It's the art of doing a political deal, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "But he is not prioritizing gun control, is he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Not prioritizing anything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", ",", "RB", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "Does New York politics meets New York media?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "I know Michael, really (ph).", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York", "New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Have you ever threaten to throw a reporter over balcony?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "I don't think I've ever threatened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 312, "question": "I'm not -- I couldn't you imagine you possibly doing that Rudy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 313, "answer": "Well, I hope I ever did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 329, "question": "And it was a moment of real unity I felt last night, wasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 330, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Denver"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 337, "question": "Who's going to win the Super Bowl?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 338, "answer": "I think Denver.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "...I guess of an innocence about it?", "question_pos_tagged": [":", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "When I turn.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mau", "Robin"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "CC", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "Is that inevitable when two of your brothers are twins?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "WRB", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "I think we became disconnected about 12 years ago and then when we lost him, Mau, Robin and I gravitated back towards each other a little bit and it's always been twins and the older brother.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP$", "''", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Is it the precious outside forces of fame and so on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "It's, I guess, its' the difference between being a group and being brothers in a group or being sisters in a group, you know.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "Why that one?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Because it's really about lost love in all young people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["BBC"], "LOCATION": ["Massachusetts"]}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "WRB", "``", "NNP", "''", "VBD", "NN", "CD", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", ":", "CC", ":", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "Why did you marry her?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "Well, we met on the set of Top of the Pops when \"Massachusetts\" was number one and then we had a cup of tea in the canteen of the BBC and then we had a couple in -- and (inaudible) and time stood still.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "And how do you manage that because -- and so, this is so listed with broken marriages, how have you managed to sustain such a lasting love do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", ":", "CC", "RB", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Because I think we've just always been in love.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "You've never looked to anyone else since she's always in love with you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Well, I think we've both loved.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 545, "question": "Hard to watch, why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "TO", "VB", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 546, "answer": "Because I hate looking at myself with different ages.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "And how's the -- how's your voice on that, I mean, how is it compared to what it used to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "It's OK.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "Did people expect you to talk about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Did you and the Beatles hang out much or not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Not really.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 611, "question": "Your brother Andy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 612, "answer": "Yeah.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 620, "question": "Is that part of the progress?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 621, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "What would be your favorite memory or perhaps the big times with your brothers, not the early days (ph)?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ":", "NN", ":", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Yeah, being around the microphone together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 686, "question": "What you would like the Bee Gees to stand forward to be remembered for, what do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 687, "answer": "A song writing, beyond anything else and harmonies, you know, there was no great approach.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 697, "question": "So, you sang it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 698, "answer": "I was the Dolly role.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "140129pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 702, "question": "But you're wearing costume?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 703, "answer": "I was not in costume.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]